winning streak
And the warriors ended with a six game winning streak
Watch out james again with that right ankle. He played last couple of games did tweak it on sunday
But he played very well in those final two games
And here's one of the fun matchups in this series anthony davis has to take a tough shot. Well defended by draymond green
And
Obviously both teams would love to get the win tonight and give it a little extra time to heal and prepare for their opponent
As andrew wingans gets inside and gets the bucket
To me, he's the key they need
25 from him tonight to be able to score enough
to win
Schruder nice play and drumming
Well a big flush down the other end and that's a welcome sight for laker fans is not anthony davis and labron james
Making every play but you get shrewder
Making plays for drumming they can be dangerous
Ken bainsmar for three that's good
You know steve kurt talking before the game knows it's a taunting task
Against a laker team when healthy they're as good as anybody in the league, but he also knows just one game
That's all you have to win. This is not a playoff series
It's a one game and move on
Schruder's jumper ball tipped and taken by draymond green
On the season warriors 39 and 33, but they finished
Winning 15 of their final 20 games in the regular season just great basketball as wingans
Knocks down another and he's playing with a lot more confidence. Look at that
He didn't wait for steph curry to make a play waved everybody out of the way
And took advantage of his matchup
James to davis davis goes right at draymond green again. Well defended davis thought he was hit
Lakers have not been dominant at home this season clearly a lot of that had to do with missing the two players
As curry pulls back, but despite all the misses as draymond green kicks it out to basemore and basemore from the elbow jumper way off
Looney has to throw it up then hit the ram and it goes in kavon looney
Very aware of the shot clock about to expire
But jeff you talked about
Without anthony davis and lebron james you were impressed as shrewder misses impressed the way the lakers kept being competitive absolutely defensively
They remained rock solid. They just had some troubles offensively
But what they've done defensively all year to be the best team in the league at that end is special
Curry throws the pass stolen by anthony davis number one rated defensive team davis for three
Rebound kept alive by drummond, but he's going to be called for a loose ball foul
Andre drummond signed at the end of march after a buyout
With the cavaliers
This is his 22nd game started all 21 games average just under 12 points little over 10 rebounds
But frank vocals is still a work in progress trying to get him comfortable and familiar with playing with his new teammates
Curry to looney
Curry using a dream on green screen nice feet inside looney shot blocked
Andre jonman with the rejection looney was ready to throw it down
James to davis
James with the tip and with the left hand and frank vocals irate. He thought david davis got fouled again
I thought it was a good block
Curry flips it up shot too strong looney back out to basemore wide open three
And vulgar wants a timeout hot start
Such so many different matchups to look at have fun. Let's let's start with steph curry jeff
How do the lakers try and guard him? What do you think their their game plan will be?
Well, the thing I think for a great defensive team like the lakers that they have to avoid is overreacting
To curry and leaving others open. That's what's happened to start this game
Meanwhile mark a big question for frank vogel and the lakers they've got the size advantage
They've got the traditional centers golden state likes to play small ball. How do you handle that if you're frank?
Well to me, I like to see him post up. Lebron james gets a smaller
Wiggins our last possession basemore defending him take advantage of that size of strength creating offense for himself as an aggressive
or for his teammates wiggins is a great defensive team and
Golden state the fifth rated defense in the nba this year
Oh and wiggins with the block of james has to fire it up and it's the side of the backboard
Great defensive play from andrew wiggins
This is a great defensive play coach. But in my opinion lebron lets him off the hook. He fades away
There's no help coming. That's one-on-one beat him on your terms go towards the basket as opposed to fading away from him
Absolutely, and the way he's going to play that's going to be a great defensive play
On your terms go towards the basket as opposed to fading away from absolutely
Wiggins had a strong finish to the season especially after the all-star break not only the defense but averaging over 20 per game
ball deflected by caldwell pulp
Wiggins guarded by james down the other end knocks down the three
Pretty good couple of sequences for andrew wiggins to start his play-in game. He's had a tremendous year
I mean
When he's the third most important player like he was in minnesota the year they went to the playoffs when he was there
It's a perfect role for him. I mean he's played exceptional basketball this year
particularly the second half of the year
Drummond puts it on the floor double team back out to davis shot clock down a three james a three-pointer way off
And ramon bringing the rebound the lakers have missed nine of their first 11 from the field
Baysmore running gets it to loonie and loonie and a held ball with anthony davis
I'm, just thinking about it think about your third best player with the ability to average 20 to 25 points
You put clay thompson with this unit watch out next year
Absolutely, and I give steve kerr a lot of credit. He's narrowed his rotation. They play eight guys now
There's more comfort level. They're an older team. They're experienced
You don't go far in the nba playoffs playing all young guys you saw clay thompson there once that injury
It changed a lot of plans for the golden state warriors
James now guarded by baysmore wiegand's helps out shrewder good ball movement here called well pope. Good luck knocks down the three
And that's what they want out of that double team I would rather stunt at anthony davis
Stay at home with called well pope and make anthony davis shoot and make threes
You see shrewder initially on steph curry. There'll be a number of players james with the deflection, but wiggins able to get it back
shock lock down to four
wiggins pull off three
And drummond rips down the rebound drummond one of the premier elite rebounders in the game throughout his career
James
Called well pulp off balance
James goes down a lane the runner and draws the foul on baysmore
Well, they get the switch and then they double and they full rotate
That's a long closeout by wiggins
again, I would have rather stunted off of
Caldwell pope and made anthony davis
Shoot the long ball
And mike did we have starting lineups earlier? Yes
I wish they were sponsored by taco bell and I could have said sponsored by taco fall
I'm surprised you waited so long to take your first shot man. You didn't come up for breath. So I
Was i've been sitting on that
It's the free throw but
Congratulations to you
On truly a hall of fame career. It was an honor to be at your induction. Absolutely. Well deserved in an incredible speech
You made us proud partner
Thank you gentlemen, but this is a fact
I couldn't have done it without you man. We don't need to hear that. That's fake hustle. That's like saying
Curry couldn't have done it without
Jordan bell. Come on
Why can't you just say thank you though as well? Thank you. No, no, you don't mean that don't say thank you
He's not sincere man. It's about him
Well, here's lead by six
True to guarding curry again curry launches a three-pointer that one off the bark for the rebound want to scott o anderson
Draymond green tries a three that misses drumming hauls in another rebound
So
Michael molder also in the game for golden state. Here's basemore
Mulder runs to the corner, but basemore banks it won't go to scott o anderson misses the tip here comes james
Schruder corner three james the offensive rebound
So
Quick move inside draws the contact shot won't go but a foul and he will go right back to the free throw line
But I don't want to sound like a broken record
But that's the type of plays he's got to make especially the way that they're defending him and I understand coming off
Injury, he's trying to feel his way through the game
But as we move closer and closer towards getting involved into this game, I expect to see labron a little bit more aggressive
Now you see those two games the last two of the regular season did tweak again the ankle on sunday, but nothing serious
So
James missing a career high 27 games only played 45 games at those 20 consecutive out with the ankle injury
Now playing in the playing game where he famously said wherever came up with this should be fired
I think the whole thing has been pretty exciting curry on the drive
Flips it up back shot is good step curry with his first field goal coach
Just look at the size difference between these two teams on the floor right now at every position
So
James finds caldwell pope another corner three another one knocking it down called well pope
Two for two from three-point range
Welcome back to warriors lakers now
If you see labron james go to the bench a little more often than usual in this first half
Coach frank vocal told me that's because the more minutes labron plays the more his ankle tends to stiffen up
So they are going to try if they don't fall too far behind here to backload his minutes and keep him under 30 total
Now you just saw the playback in march where he got initially hurt. This is where he tweaked it again just three days ago
LeBron told us he hadn't stopped thinking about the way this injury derailed his season
He had to rehab for more than six weeks and said quote I hated every moment of it
But mike he said he's ready to move forward and he doesn't anticipate his movement being limited in any real way tonight
Thank you. Rachel. You forget how well he was playing
Prior to the injury how well the lakers were playing prior to the injury to james and davis. They were 21 and 6
Caruso wide open nobody near him and he cans the three
and they did
On that one stay at home on caldwell pope, but caruso shot the ball very well from three this year
draymond green gets inside and draws the foul
on andre drummond
And green's shaking up
Well good stunt by basemore
But caruso again really improved as a three-point shooter
So green will go to the line
Green has had one outstanding season, especially defensively when he hits the first our upcoming national tv schedule tnt tomorrow
indiana and washington
And that game
After indiana with the victory washington losing to boston then espn friday. Memphis will play the loser of this game
It's a nine eastern start and will be either in san francisco or here at the staples center
I'll tell you indiana played a great
Offensive game down three of their main guys. So bonus
He's a great
Great offensive player. Absolutely
They started off great and did not let their foot off the gas pedal davis after kuzma kyle kuzma montrezl harrell in the game
Raymond green on davis one-on-one excellent defense again stolen by basemore
So
Basemore goes right at davis throws up a wild shot and draws the foul anthony davis picking up his first
That is outstanding defense by draymond green one-on-one against anthony davis for the second time
You just you just battle them and you stay in front and don't give them anything easy active hands
Secure your position be disciplined and give your team a chance exactly what he did
Basemore in the starting lineup
As colin state has some injuries kelly ubre still out with the left wrist. He's going to be reevaluated next week
James wiseman, of course their center out for the season with right knee surgery. Damian lee also out and of course that man
Missing his second consecutive year
Can't wait to see him back in uniform running up and down the floor
And they need him and you look at this game. For example, the war is not going to win if step curry
Doesn't get going at some point the lakers are forcing him to get rid of the basketball where he sees bodies in front of him
The sconnow anderson misses the three called paul pulp the rebound
They're doing a good job of keeping two people he comes off a pick and roll
They don't leave them until he gets rid of the basketball
Step curry's taking just three shots so far
Mulder some early minutes guarding caruso
So
Caldwell pope nice screen set by davis step back jumper won't go
Green has been absolutely great defensively
Curry against kuzma. There's a double team second turnover by curry
Kuzma to caruso drives inside lefty layup is good. It goes crashing right focal again saying where was the whistle lot of contact there
And caruso off the bench with five points
The active hands come up with the steal and good delivery by kuzma
Russo with the finish that's clearly contact. You should be going to the line
Curry double again
Ramon green fakes davis right there
Five on the 24 curry fakes the three gets away from davis off one foot too strong
And here comes kuzma lakers have made it difficult early for steph curry
Kuzma a three-pointer
And a loose ball foul is going to go against curry
And coach, you know people say well, how can you get them going?
Well, you can get them going by getting stops defensively and pushing the basketball is tougher to trap pick and rolls
When you're pushing it in transition and a technical foul, I believe on draymond green
Green gosh, tibbinson. I don't want to hear it
Green now trying to talk
Whatever happened to the parent that says I don't want to hear it then you still talking they said I said I don't want to hear
That's the end of it. He just gave him an extra candy bar
That foul by the way was on molder not curry as davis hits the technical free throw and now
Much more
Pleasant conversation
josh, tibbinson and I have a difference of opinion of what no more means
Josh, tibbinson has become one of the premier officials in the nba in recent years
And you get a technical and since we don't count this as the playoffs it doesn't count against any suspension so you can
These are freebies
Trueter in there up top to caruso
And throws it back in the corner
And throws it out of bounds he's talking about the playing stats do not count toward the regular season and do not count toward the playoffs
They kind of fade away I suppose but it's also, you know, it's the same for the broadcast. So whatever you say
It's okay. You can say whatever you want. It's not it's not recorded. He does that in any way mike. I'm just saying they should count
I saw jason tatum's 50 as molder dumps it counts
Put them in the postseason. This is the postseason
I'm in agreement with you. I think they're uh, they're trying to figure out what's the best way
I just figured it out for them. I'm just staying with their thinking curry on the rebound. This is miss
Curry way downtown in and out and davis the rebound
Lakers shooting just 32 from the field, but they're only down by three
Shrewder misses the three
Montrezl harrell spins flips it up shot won't go tipped by kuzma and another offensive rebound which he's been doing all season
And curry the rebound curry averaged a career high five and a half rebounds per game this year
Gets inside draws the foul count it and one
And to me that's the most underrated two things about his game the rebounding aspect and the finishing aspect
Is that he's got a great
That's just beautiful
Touch around the rim this year. He became the oldest scoring champion in the nba in 23 years
When michael jordan was 35 he finished the season with 46 points on sunday against memphis
He was just absolutely sensational. Of course a lot of the talk this week. Lebron james saying the other day
MVP he had the best season all year. Well, he's had an incredible season and it's it's a joy to cover him and watch him
As davis knocks down the little floater. He was 0 for 6. Sam fitty davis before that shot and it's back to four
But I like what he did instead of posting screen on the ball
And get some space from green
Want to scott o anderson knocks down a three turns and says something to the fans and runs down the floor
He has one been a one of the great stories this year in the nba
The east oakland native now playing for his team that he grew up rooting for
Schruder shot block to scott o anderson saves it but right to harold blocked by green but a foul
Again two free throws coming up for la
See the great ball movement and
The young fella gets it done oakland's finest
Proud to be a warrior. Well this happy ending for him. He just signed a multi-year contract to play for the team again
Growing up rooted for his undrafted out of marquette back in 2015 took him five years to get to the nba
mexico argentina venezuela the g league
And he has become so much more than an energy player. Bob myers absolutely loves him
He's got terrific skill. He's extremely smart. Draymond green says he changes the game with his intensity
And steve kerr says I trust him
It's been a great story and he's the one guy that can do draymond green type things on the floor
Initiating offense setting screens extra pass
What a fine by the warriors
Steve Kerr actually calls him a mini draymond green
You think I just freestyled that mike well, I wanted to give a little credit come on loonie the rebound
six point warriors lead
It was about a five-second difference between the shot clock and game clock
Very just two for six to start
Mulder wiggins
Rebound shrewder final seconds. No fouls to give here shooter ahead to davies
Davis three pointers up shot short
Welcome back to the state farm nba play-in tournament. I'm rachel nichols here with coach steve
Her great start you guys got out to steve. What was working for you?
Well, I thought our defense was really good rachel and it's been good, you know the last few weeks and that's uh,
That's what we have to play off of so our guys did a good job
What's your approach to the size disadvantage that your team has here tonight?
Well, we just got to make sure everybody's engaged all the time and you know keeping everyone off the glass they're they're obviously
Much bigger and stronger than we are but if we're active and we're boxing out with all five guys we can hold our own
Thanks so much steve. All right back to you. Mike. Thank you rachel fifth turnover for golden state
James five points in that first quarter tail important tucker out there with james shrewder kuzma
And harold
Horton tucker straight on three. That's good. This young man's having
An excellent season in terms of taking some steps, but the three-pointer
Has been at times a struggle for him nice shot there and it's a three-point game
Jordan pulled the floater
Looney's follow misses harold the rebound no curry. No green with james on the floor
This is going to be a challenge
James drives you can't get it and kavon looney grabs another rebound seven rebounds already for kavon looney. They'll need him
With the size advantage of the lakers
Mulder catch and shoot that's good three-pointer from mulder. He can shoot the second-year guard from kentucky
Well, you look at this unit on the floor for the warriors right now
No curry or green, but they have the ability to get the ball in the middle of the field
Warriors right now no curry or green
But they have the ability to compete at a high level spread the floor and they have shooting all around
Shruder drives shrewder misses looney grabs another defensive rebound
And interestingly they have tiskano anderson on shrewder
Pool has it eight to shoot tiskano anderson not that time fight for the rebound. Come on looney
Nine rebounds now already another three
Mulder can't get it to go
Six point golden state lead with two minutes into the second
They played each other three times warriors won the first game lakers two blowouts after that, but both teams obviously so radically different now
So
Kuzma
And it hit one of the wires atop the backboard so it's golden state ball
Stop curry talking about the the warriors. She said back in
In february march. It was a little bleak, but he's so proud of the way this team just kept fighting
And he says now we've given ourselves a chance
To make this season matter curry and green the leadership they showed
And the warriors turned it around
The scano anderson feet inside
Looney shot in and out. LeBron james rips down the rebound. That's outstanding possession though. Great ball movement making plays for one another
Just wasn't able to finish. It's tiskano anderson
Like you mentioned before mark can really?
pass and make plays
Montrezl harrell
foul by looney
And the former six-man winner with the clippers will go to the line
It has not been an easy adjustment for montrezl last year played so well for the la clippers this year
He's had some some good stretches. His numbers are solid not playing as many minutes not getting as much touches
But it's been inconsistent at times. Well three centers makes it a challenge for the coaching staff
and for the three players
And I think the thing if i'm if i'm harrell my mentality has got to be
The way I got paid and made it in this league
I gave great energy great effort great enthusiasm from day one
So I was a difference maker because of the way I went about my business
He's got to get back to being that then he's a handful to defend
And I think it's interesting too. I think the challenge going forward
For the coaching staff is at times last year
They played with
As a free throw rebound's given up they played with anthony davis at center
So now that they have three other centers
Do you ever get back to that lineup right? It's basically four centers that
All feel they deserve time horton tucker goes inside flips it up and an offensive foul is called
Well tucker picks up the personal frank vogel obviously disagrees with the call
Morton tucker wants to see the replay
Not a lot there
To me, that's not a defensive foul
But it's not an offensive foul either
Pool to wiggins wiggins trying to slam a shot block porton tucker right there minimum of the rim and then a foul
As wiggins goes crashing to the floor
I like wiggins trying to attack like that
So attacking the rim
Good job of going vertical
But I like like you talked about here
They need him to be aggressive on the offensive end
Bow was on caruso
Caruso picks up his first
Here's pool and pool is fouled before any shot attempt caruso trying to fight over the screen picks up his second
And I agree with the lake is defensively right now
You have to treat jordan pool the way you treat
Steph curry with that first unit because he's a guy that can get hot and then the rim opens up for him
Pull the last six games average 20 a game
He had a career high 38 last week
You know with curry on the bench frank vocal said he's kind of taken over like the cj mccollum
Roll in terms of when lillard goes to the bench mccollum has to score they need pool to score
Not that time as kuzma gets the rebound
Not that he was comparing him to cj mccollum
portent tucker
short on the through
Here's pool inside the arc
Six on the 24
Wiggins against caruso nice spin move and finish from andrew wiggins. He's got nine points. He has a great right to left spin
Harold
Knocked away ball picked up to scott o anderson
Two-on-one break goes right at lebron james and finishes
And a timeout call by frank vocal
They got a lot of doubt down there. We got we got a lot of belief good job guys good quarter
Holding our own on the boards defending without fouling all good stuff
He has been proud of this team talked about, you know disjointed early. Obviously the injury to clay thompson
He said that they've come together really well as the season went on. He kept telling the team late in the season
We're going to go on a run. We're going to go on a run and they finished 15 and five in those last 20 games
And I like how wiggins is picking up full court
On occasions james drives gets inside block by tesco anderson knocked out of bounds still laker ball
This is just good verticality boy this kid is tough
Warriors have five block shots already
James gets inside bank shot missed it ball tipped out to scott o anderson pushing it up the floor
Mulder pool to scott o anderson out there with loonie and wiggins wiggins fires a three way off
And it's laker ball and you look at this game right now with seven minutes to go on in the second quarter
One team is getting after it like they want it and the other team is in chill mode
And if you're the lakers you have to respond because the warriors are here
to advance to sunday
Kuzma gets that one to go prior to that shot. The lakers were shooting 24 from the field. They had missed eight shots in a row
That's a very strong assertive move by kuzma
Wiggins to loonie tescano anderson can't get the three montrezl harrell with the board
Montrezl harrell with the board
James finds montrezl harrell inside and throws it down in a crowd
This first field goal
Timeout call by steve curve
The warriors are shooting 38 29 from three and steph curry has five points
Now both these teams their defense has been a big part of their success as we mentioned lakers number one defensive rating and the warriors
number five
Pool goes right out drumming layup is good. Top shot from jordan pool
Lakers looking to push the other way steve kurt talked about that. He wants his team to really push the tempo tonight
Shruder gets some room davis tries the three
Davis have not shot the ball well from three since his return from the camp injury
Curry finds some room gets inside draws the foul banker won't go he's mad at himself, but he'll get two free throws
And that's two straight pick and rolls
That drumming has been ineffective in defending. He's got to get down a little bit lower. He has great feet
He can do this
But he can't reach and get himself out of position
Curry has talked this year. It's the best he's felt physically and the best he is seeing the game this year
And the year off last year
Might have helped him get the ball
Last year
Might have helped
That as well only five games played with a broken hand. There's no question it re-energized
And you know players will talk about this guys who play in the finals year after year the grind of that lebron james
That's one of the unbelievable things about what he's able to do. It's almost like another season
And it has recharged him
So
Dennis shrewder trying to get going still looking for his first field goal throws it away green with the steel
That's great pick and roll defense. I mean that's superior
Ability to play to play the ball handler and play the role man
You
See shrewder he's got to come off the score green stunning at him and recovering that's beautiful that's outstanding
Steve kurt talks about it all the time. He knows what the opponent is running
He blows up opponents plays all the time nice feet inside, but basemore rushed it
Although davis's presence had something to do with that caldwell pulp three-pointer short right back to him up top to shrewder
And he's going to get a little bit more into the ball
Caldwell pulp pass inside broke it up basemore this time got a hand on it
Boy active hands again from the warriors pool explodes to the rim and finishes
Jordan, pull his second field goal and it's back to a 10-point warriors lead the lakers have 30 points
And there's under five to play in the first half
Caruso barely had it in his hand knocks down the three i'm looking at that last possession anthony davis has kent
Basemore on him and comes out to send a high screen roll a side screen and roll. Oh, give me the basketball
It's your time to be a little bit more aggressive
The sconnell anderson basemore fakes drives on caruso leans in on drum and flips it up way off
And
An offensive foul is going to be called on anthony davis and frank bogle hot once again
Well right now draymond green is putting on a master's class on how to defend
He has taken anthony davis out of the ballgame now that's that's that's just a smart play
He puts himself in position to take the hit
But he is in the head of anthony davis thus far and some joy going on right now and a technical foul
We'll hand it out double technical
John goebel came in. I believe it's on davis and tuscano anderson. The warriors are saying why is it a double technical?
If you're draymond green, you don't want to get caught in this you already have a technical foul yourself
So it is on davis, but the other one's on pool jordan pool
And the other one's on the ballgame
And the other one is on the ballgame
That's like the old line when the nca got really mad at kentucky. They put cleveland state on probation
Curry for three his first three-pointer of the half and from way downtown
LeBron james back in
Schruder 0 for 7. It's james guarded by tescano anderson
Leans in excellent defense throws it away
Boy, this colin state defense as you said mark, they're putting on a clinic here in the first half
five to shoot for the lakers
So
Shot clock winding down and pool with a foul with 3.4 remaining on the shot clock
Davis gets that one to go just his second field goal. He was one for nine prior to that. It's an eight-point game
Despite the horrific shooting by the lakers, especially their stars again. They're only down eight curry
Another three back to back threes for step curry. Now. He's got 12
And this equals the largest lead of the first half
Wiggins back in now curry switches on james
the two former mvps
Davis against wiggins
Davis settles for the jump shot and rebound to scott. Oh anderson
Green beautiful pass ahead to scott. Oh anderson stripped by caldwell pope
Schruder tries a three
And then schruder still without a field goal. James to davis davis blocked green got a piece of it
And the warriors go the other way
Another forced turnover by golden state curry gets inside blocked by struder here comes caruso the other way caruso
Almost tried an alley-oop to himself
Somehow managed to get the layup to go. He did alley-oop until himself got away with it, which is fine
You can throw it up
But I I tell you what green not giving james a dunk
to me as
next level intelligence
Graham on green cross court to pool pool for three knocks it down a three-pointer for golden state
Now the golden state warriors showing once again why they've been one of the best defensive teams
In the nba this season led by dream on green and guys you got to figure and watch so much basketball
He's one of the smartest defensive players i've seen in in all my years covering the nba
Well, I had the privilege of coaching him so i'm well aware from day one his instincts his intelligence superior
True to the drive
Nearly another forced turnover, but called well pulp has it and a whistle and a foul. Let's check in with rachel
Mike, this is so interesting according to all the tracking data. We have now if you look over the past eight years
No one has defended anthony davis on more plays than yep
Draymond green so draymond told me that that means there's no surprises ad knows all of his little tricks
He knows all of anthony's instead. He said quote what it's going to boil down to in this game
It boils down to heart it boils down to who wants it more it boils down to who can out think the guy
Other guy on a particular play
He said it's not that I will go and say I don't know what he's capable of
I know what he's capable of draymond said it's can I stop him?
And as you guys have noted tonight, we've seen a clinic draymond's been doing that work mike
Thank you. Rachel as wiggins picks up the foul james hits the free throw
He just seems to shine come playoff time and he looks for these type of games these type of matchups
But you know what? He knows also coach. He knows that
And it's his advantage when it comes down to heart and it's no disrespect to anthony davis
But he he has a fight his chance in that situation if it boils down to talent. It's anthony davis all day long
And he's got a good line up there
He's got a good line up there
Laker's shooting 30 from the field 29 from three
And they have 38 points with a minute and a half to play in the second curry three-pointer two strong rebound caruso
Davis comes back to caruso
And caruso
Caldwell pulp corner three is up shot. No good and wiggins with a rebound and great block out by tiskano anderson
You don't see blocking out
But he eliminated davis's size with that block out wiggins nice turnaround shot wouldn't go james looks to lead the break the other way
Pass inside caruso layup tough shot able to get it off the glass caruso is their leading score
And their only player double figures with 12
And that's a good sign if you're the golden state warriors game plan discipline
And I like this lineup with davis at five
A lot more from a spacing standpoint
Pool cross card, it's kind of anderson with five to shoot and hits the three-pointer law to scott o anderson eight points off the bench
Back to 12 with 25 seconds remaining
The three leading scores for the la lakers james davis intruder three for 27 from the field
Trueter the drive layup is good tough shot. He finally gets one to go. He was 0 for 8
And i'm not allowing steph curry to play one on one in this situation
Either are they curry step back three bang at the buzzer
Steph curry from downtown and the warriors will take a 13-point lead into halftime
What a first half for golden state
Defensively putting on a clinic and then curry coming alive from free point range in the second period
Baze more steps back three-pointer way off rebound loonie, but he's called for a push
looney, by the way had 11 rebounds in that first half as he picks up his second coach if I was
Dennis shrewder lebron james anthony davis looking at what we talked about the impact in that first half i'd cut off the coach
The coach's speech in the locker room at halftime and i'd look and say i've got to be better
I've got to do a better job of taking care of my business forget about what's on the board
Again considering those numbers they're fortunate to be only down by 13 as we've seen in the nba
13 points is not a huge deficit to overcome
As the shot clocks down to four shrewder drives on wiggins
And a foul
I'll take it on the side
We'll send it over to rachel
Well mike i'm told there was plenty of excitement as the warriors piled into the locker room coming off that great
Step shot to close the first half
But i'm also told it only lasted about 15 seconds and then steve kerr got everyone to buckle down and refocus
No major adjustments for the warriors, but he did tell the team prepare for the lakers to make some runs here
They're a championship team. We just have to weather them meanwhile over on the lakers side the coaching staff told players
They got to be more physical against this warrior squad. They do have that size advantage, but they also told the guys just relax
Just relax we're missing wide open shots just
Ease into it here. These are shots that you can make mike
Thank you, rachel this draymond green picked up the foul initially josh tibbens said
It was on the floor but talked with his fellow officials. They changed it to the act of shooting
No, he got bullied by lebron james into asking. No, that's that's the real deal
That's another way of putting it and they changed the call and i'm not saying it wasn't the right call
I'm saying that's why
They discussed it and I would have a different message for the lakers. I wouldn't say relax. I would say we're too relaxed
Let's do something
No doubt warriors look like the hungry team curry saves it but right to shooter on an erin pass from green
And here comes james
James gets into the paint mid-range jumper shot one goal loonie another rebound quick outlet to curry
Curry to base more attacks the rim layup shot. No good
Golden state looking to push it every opportunity
Shruder draws the foul shot won't go but step curry will pick up his second personal
and that's been a problem for golden state all year, which is
fouling too much
And to start this half
They haven't made them make shots they put shrewder to the line twice sure missed 14
Days down the stretch with the health and safety protocols played the last two games, but his conditioning is far from where it should be
So
Shruder led the team in scoring when lebron james was out mark. They need him to be super aggressive
Absolutely out of pick and rolls in transition
At their best he's that third option and at times carries them offensively
Curry to green green try to jam it
James and drumming right there james down the other end lamp locked a foul counted and one stolen down
And a chance for a three-point play and suddenly it's just a seven-point game with a free throw
The coach a recipe for disaster if you're the warriors
Allowing the lakers to get to the free throw line turning the basketball over and giving them easy opportunities in transition
Sometimes teams in this league frustrate me
But what the utah jazz just did by giving out?
full ride scholarships
to underserved kids
Is a home run that the whole league
Should adopt absolutely
When the players were calling the kids I looked at that video
And I was absolutely so proud of utah
And the players I just thought it was brilliant
So special for those young men and women as wiggins spins and backs at home
Back up to eight for golden state warriors have led the entire game
Lakers have not led the largest lead
Is 13
Right now 57 49 called well pulp to james james kicks it out
Caldwell pulp off the bounce running lap is good sweet bowl from contagious called well pulp
He's got eight points and I like that offensive set by
Los angeles having james as the screener
When he's the screener it is really hard to guard pick and roll curry behind the back flips it up and
Went a little short as davis grabs the rebound and especially the screener with curry involved it puts you in the dilemma defensively
James to davis davis three-pointer won't go
Lakers just five of 19 from downtown golden state has hit twice as many threes
Dangerous pass stolen by called well pope called well pope down the other end layup block but a foul
Raymond green upset after the turnover the called wall pulp will shoot a couple of free throws
But again, we're talking about a team that's struggling to score you're giving them opportunities
Carelessness on the offensive end by the warrens and they're already the lakers are already in the penalty
So they're showing up to the top of the game
And the lakers are already in the penalty so they're shooting the rest
Of the quarter while la hasn't committed a team foul. No golden state already five team fouls
And called well pope's numbers
One of these teams tonight will earn the seventh seed in the west and the right to
Get into the nba playoffs and you can watch the nba playoffs starting saturday on abc
espn tnt
And nba tv the winner tonight
Will face phoenix
That game one will be sunday time to be determined in phoenix against the suns
Just a spectacular season they finished second utah finished one
These two teams in the playing
shrewder against
Wiggins playing physical wig and spins tied up shot clock at five green another turnover
As davis brings it into the front court
Back up shrewder puts up the three puts it in
Dennis shrewder just his second field goal
And it's a one-point game
You get into rhythm at the free throw line. So he caught a rhythm at the free throw line
And now he knocks in the three
And a foul down the other end
Crowd doesn't like it. There's about six thousand fans here at the staples center tonight
And this is just a wide open
Catch and shoot three and mike you mentioned six thousand fans. I also love
That they have they were able to get more fans because they have what a vaccinated section. Yep. I I love that
Curry step back three-pointer and his foul
Shruder commits the personal that's going to be his first and curry will shoot three free throws
First personal second team and I thought he kicked out his leg. I would really think about challenging that
He does get into that landing area
And mike you talked about the winner playing the phoenix sons want to say congratulations to coach mondy williams who the coaches
Voted him as the coach of the year. Yep his season in nba a job well done and an award well deserved
Absolutely
Terrific job and I love their whole team attitude. They weren't trying to to manipulate the standings
Whoever comes our way comes our way
How about the season chris paul has had for that team?
Meanwhile, these two coaches
A little chess match right now
Curry hits all three lead back up to four
18 points for curry
As a successful coach in this league for so many years
Did you ever try to manipulate the standings and see who he was going to match up with now? I just
I had a like just whether I was right or wrong that whole
Karma
As anthony davis takes another three. I I just didn't believe in it
If you want to if you're if you're a player that's going to be a player that's going to be a player that's going to be
But I think there's some
m Landry
changed
is
the
Big terminal
I was really stuck with my
My standing and jIT
I just didn't believe in it. If you want to if you're if you're a championship mentality,
I just think you got to play everybody
Blocked by looney drumm and try to get it to go. He thought he was fouled again
And the left spin.
Wiggins one on one with LeBron James,
who's just two of nine from the field.
Jumper is good.
He's gotta look at it like it's disrespectful.
As good a defender as Wiggins is,
you're gonna play me one on one?
Recognize who I am.
Take it personal.
Shruder gets right up into Curry.
Curry splits the defense.
Curry's first pass stolen by Caldwell Pope.
That's nine turnovers.
Now for the Warriors.
Four of them already here in his third quarter.
We played just five minutes.
Shruder baseline jumper is short.
Curry triple team finds Looney.
Touch pass to Baysmore.
Corner three is good.
Baysmore with his third three pointer.
And now Frank Vogel wants a time out.
The lead right back up to seven.
The 11th three pointer for Golden State.
You know what I'd like too?
The sweatsuits that the Warriors are wearing
with paying homage to Oakland.
That's pretty good.
I love that.
Drummond hands off Caldwell Pope.
Double team him.
And now Shruder across the lane.
Shot clock down to seven.
Shruder given some room.
Hesitated.
Shot clock at two.
Caruso on the drive.
On the pull up shot way off.
And a 24 second violation.
Another excellent defensive sequence from Golden State.
But I thought Shruder cooperated.
He had a couple of shots that he turned down
instead of being aggressive.
And I'll tell you what I find interesting.
Didn't they say before the game
that they wanted to limit LeBron James to 28 or 30 minutes?
He only has eight minutes left.
He's sitting right now.
He played 17 and a half minutes in the first half.
And 22 overall so.
Wiggins against Caruso.
Wiggins nice feet inside.
Looney gathers.
And throws up a shot off the glass.
Just his second field goal.
But Looney's played some excellent defense
and he has 12 rebounds.
And they missed him earlier in the possession
by Green on a slip.
Drummond across the lane.
Flips it up and in.
Four points for Drummond.
Curry gets away from the double team.
Continues left handed off the glass.
Won't go.
Chipped in by Kavon Looney.
Looney part of those championship teams.
He's got the corporate knowledge.
Drummond calling for it.
One on one with Looney.
Spins in the paint.
Falls down.
Lost it.
And Baysmore fouled by Schroeder.
And if I'm the Warriors,
you're doing me a favor.
Posting up Drummond against Looney.
I know he scored the last possession.
But if I'm Anthony Davis,
I've got to look to be aggressive
and demand the basketball.
This is not a winning recipe, coach.
I agree.
If you can get them to post Drummond,
that plays away from their strength.
But again, I like this.
Inserting the highly intense Wes Matthews
and putting Anthony Davis at the center position.
Matthews' first minutes tonight.
Curry long distance.
That's a three.
Steph Curry.
This fourth three pointer of the game.
It's back up to a dozen.
Toscano, Anderson, and Mulder back in now.
Stripped by green and stolen.
Ball loose.
Picked up by Curry.
Knocked out of his hands by Caruso.
Caldwell, Pope to Caruso.
Cross court, Matthews.
Matthews for three.
Talk about an instant contribution.
And that's a huge turn of events.
Up 12, all the momentum going in transition.
Curry turns it over and then a three.
Caruso steal on that.
An important play.
And then a foul called on Caldwell, Pope.
Frank Vogel irate again.
I'm looking at the sideline and you see greatness in Drake
and Michael B. Jordan just shaking their head
at Chef Curry with a shot.
And the response, Caruso to Matthews.
Knocked down shot, giving the Lakers life.
Matthews in his first year and there they are.
And the
court side, Draymond Green blocked by Davis.
Anthony Davis sensational defensive play.
And Green usually gets a layup of game off that fake
to Curry.
Davis calling for it, gets it inside.
Shots good and one.
Davis at both ends and a chance for a three point play.
Davis only 36 games played during the regular season missed 36
30 of them with that right calf
He was starting to show signs last final games of the season at that 42-point game against phoenix
He has struggled so far tonight, but still a long way to go
Six point warriors lead four minutes to play pass inside to curry missed the layup but a foul we got to show that
That is brilliance moving without the basketball and not a foul a goal tending
I mean, that's right mark. So two points for curry. It's just so good
If more guys were willing to move at the speed and the consistency of curry they'd be rewarded too matthews misses
So
Curry stumbles a bit now keeps his dribble alive against davis lost it ball deflected and a backcourt violation
Well curry's been loose with the ball
This quarter, but this is brilliant comes off the initial screen
Sets it up like he's going to come off the stagger back cuts
that's just
Well anthony davis was saying, you know, usually when a guy gives up the ball the defender can relax a little bit
He goes but that's when steph curry is his most dangerous after he gives up the ball
And I know I said it before but think about it you add clay thompson who moves in a similar form and fashion
The pressure that they put on your defense collectively
Is unmatched in the history of this game?
Matthews to davis scarred by tiskano anderson green looking to help
Davis spins contested shot way off that one at the side of the backboard and green gets the rebound
A well-timed double team by green on the baseline side davis now three for 16 to scott o anderson pass the base more
A lot of contact over in the far side base more three-pointer won't go davis the rebound
Under three to play here on the third
Alex caruso goes all the way blocked by green base more the other way
Train on green again just putting on a defensive clinic
Plus six assists five rebounds gets inside layup. He missed it
Ball knocked out of bounds still golden state ball
Green thought he was fouled
As caruso turned in the corner
Sees green
That's outstanding defense and help by draymond green has been doing it all night long. That's his third block
Warriors have eight to shoot jordan pool has come in
Lebron james back in
Pass inside to wigens stolen by james. That's the seventh turnover here in the third. They only had five the first half kuzma to davis
The fast break can be lethal for the lakers and they've cut the deficit to six and the warriors lose this game
They're going to look at this quarter and recognize this is where it happened carelessness on the offensive end
Another turnover but warriors are going to be able to get the ball back in the corner
And the second half of the season
Another turnover
But warriors get it back wigens for three
Under two to play third quarter here in this playing game kuzma backdoor layup is good
Time out golden state
The marquee matchup of the plan is not disappointed
Curry tied up gets it inside the green green to wigens wigens hard off the glass won't go the tip is up and good
Boy wigens playing with a force tonight at both ends. He's got 15. It's a six-point warriors lead
Matthews cuts looking for davis
James three-pointer puts it in
his first three-pointer
Of the night and it's a three-point game, but you look at the post up play what wigens had on one-on-one. He shoots a
Fade away one leg a shot
Now knocks down a three that's good defense. Sometimes you just got to give credit to greatness
Oh curry beautiful pass but wigens couldn't handle it and kuzma comes the other way
Fade away
Lob it in davis throws it down wakers within one
Boy, is it fun to hear a large crowd the noise of that once again curry on the drive
Curry for three that's good. Steph curry from way downtown his fifth three-pointer of the night
I mean other great NBA players
Can't shoot that he is one of a kind on that type of pass it sprint catch and fire
James back to order Caruso another backdoor cut leads to a layup
but there's more space on the floor now that the traditional center is out and
So there's more cutting avenues no fouls to give here for the Lakers dream on green wide open for three
Welcome back to the State Farm NBA play-in tournament here with coach Frank Vogel Frank
What do you attribute that lockdown defense in the third quarter? You really forced a bunch of Warriors turnovers?
Yeah, that's a pretty good most of the night. We wrapped it up a little bit in that quarter
We know that steps border to get going still hit a few bombs on us
You know, we got to live with that but you know, our guys are motivated and you know
Do or die fourth quarter a playoff berth on the line you've got Steph Curry on the other side
What do you tell your guys gonna execute?
Okay, just that's what you got to worry about get our defensive coverage is and get a good shot every time down
Thank you so much
All right, Rachel James the rebound after the beautiful feed to Davis to tie the game opening minute here fourth quarter
Warriors
largest lead was 13 early in the third and
The Warriors did a good job when curry and green rested in the first half
But this is danger zone right now James inside bank shot missed it and come on looney could not quite hold on
And it's Laker ball with 14 now on the shot clock
And I love this substitution of draymond green coming back in that's just a beautiful pass to Davis
You need to match greens minutes with Davis
Kuzma trying to get free and they lob it into Kuzma over pool lays it up and in
You know Lakers with their first lead of the night
How long does Steve Kerr leave Steph Curry out at his ballgame
That's the ninth assists from LeBron James Mulder to pool
Pulls been excellent off the bench down the stretch of the regular season. It's a whole different ballgame
Mulder harassed and stolen by Caruso the turnovers continue to mount the second half for the Warriors
And this is where Wiggins was stationary that entire possession
He's got to be great when curry rest James drives on Toscano Anderson layup banks at home
timeout Golden State
Wiggins battling with Matthews Matthews an excellent defender throughout his career
Wiggins trying to draw foul didn't get the whistle
We said a lot about the lake the Warriors turning the ball over you got to give credit to this lake of defense
They have increased the volume and I think it starts with who you're playing. So West Matthews
He has been intense as James goes in with the reverse
And there's more room on the floor
Now six-point lead that's a 19-point turnaround here on the second half curry looking to Scott O Anderson driving layup
offensive foul James draws the charge
Davis falls on top of them
And I think Steve Kerr may be challenging this and that's a block
It is going to be a challenge
So they'll challenge those guys will get up and we'll see what happens
Eight points five rebounds off the bench
It's only the 11th and 12th free throws of the game for Golden State
Second half so far
They haven't played mantras harrell. They haven't played
Porton Tucker, they've gone with a very tight rotation
Steve Kerr has only played eight players
His team trails by five two and a half gone by in the fourth Caruso the drive
Davis the tip won't go to Scott O Anderson a rebound again Draymond Green contesting the shot
Curry back into green
Davis on curry
Green pass tried to thread the needle and turned it over
I had beautiful feet to Matthews good transition defense though from the Warriors
Kuzma the drive can't finish
Wiggins back to the corner
Wiggins
Barrels into Matthews offensive foul
Boy, what a call from Frank Volga to get West Matthews off the bench
He has really had an impact as a coach
You have to have guys that you trust that when is when it matters most I know exactly what they're going to do
And West Matthews has been proven to be a competitor at an elite level
And a guy that has no quit and he has come out and got it done on a defensive end especially
This is why they signed him. It's his first year with the Lakers
He's 34 his 12th year in the league. The Lakers are his seventh team. He's always been an excellent defensive player
tough fearless
Rob Palenka
Wanted to ring him for these kind of games. There's certain matchups. You need him defensively can also hit a three
Competitors only apply it's hard to find great competitors West Matthews is
Davis jump shot got it Anthony Davis has come alive in the second half
You know Laker lead is seven
Curry for three answers
Steph Curry with a six three-pointer
He's got 29 when he cleared a whole side eliminate the help and allow Steph Curry to win his matchup one-on-one and Caruso
Was substituted out of the game?
Curry on Davis isolated there on the elbow Wiggins looking to help pool comes over to help
Matthews inside Kuzma shot clock at four Kuzma tough fall away shot in and out
Now the fight for the rebound goes to Draymond Green
Curry on the drive scoop layup he banks at home all what a sweet move from curry
31 points and it's a two-point game
And
Pool just pushing Matthews out of the way
That's going to be the first team foul here on the fourth no Caruso
Arassing him through to insert it into the game Steph Curry knocks down the three gets a rhythm
Then keeps them off balance turns the corner
Spectacular finish before the contest an efficient game for curry 10 of 18 from the field six of nine from three
Davis left alone for three got it
Anthony Davis his first three-pointer of the night he was all for five and it's back to a five-point Laker leave
Get a couple of layups get a dunk and now the jump shot becomes a little bit
Easier he struggled from three-point range all season long
Just 26%
well good find by James as
Green tries to take away the role
Always chatting away who's straight on green
Curry gets free drives inside scoop layup missed it. He thought he was hit see her is furious
Here's James the other way long three-pointer
Caroms out to Mulder
Jordan poor all beautiful crossover tried to jam it ball knocks loose out of bounds
And it's gonna be Warriors ball
That would have been quite the highlight for Jordan pool
I'm giving him a point just for the move and he got found
How was that not a foul
Why are you looking at me? I'm not reffing Wiggins pull on the inbound and it's back to three
I
True to brings it up with 643 remaining the Bron James sitting right now
Well, he's at his minute limit
I wonder if we'll see him again entry pass knocked away by Draymond Green pull ahead to Wiggins Wiggins drives floats it up shot is good
19 points for Wiggins and it's back to one timeout LA
Marv Albert the greatest basketball announcer of all time
Whose impact on aspiring broadcasters is immeasurable?
Congratulations. Thanks for a spectacular career Marv Albert
And I'm one of those guys three years with Marv Albert as a partner
congratulations legend
Paul misses screen dives Kuzma no comes up with it
Just past the midway point of the fourth Schroeder draws the foul shot won't go
I'm just trying to imagine you as a head coach of the Lakers right now
What the looks you would be given LeBron James like basically asking while you are you ready yet?
No, I wouldn't be giving him dirty looks I'd be given that
Whoever's in charge of the minutes police. I'd be like
Come on now. We'll give him off tomorrow
And the next day as Caruso is gonna come back in to the game
Schroeder has struggled tonight just two of eleven from the field, but it's the free-throw Lakers back up to
Caruso will come in and Matthews sits 11 minutes for Matthews, but he made his presence felt I
Think the key obviously was the Lakers activity, but I think Frank Vogel found for this game
Davis at five playing huge minutes already up to 36 and
Going to West Matthews
Was a huge factor in
their swarming defense
Schroeder goes one for two
Caruso back in the guard curry
Finds Wiggins Wiggins gets inside draws the contact and banks at home chance for a three-point play
Big plays from Wiggins on both ends of the floor tonight
An unselfishness of Steph Curry takes the double-team gets rid of the basketball
Wiggins aggressive turns the corner and if you're anybody on a lake is not defending curry
You have to pull all the way over so he doesn't have ability to catch and finish
Wiggins wants to get the victory get back in the playoffs
He's only been in the playoffs once in his first six years in the league
That was five games in the first round with Minnesota in 2018
He has had a terrific season. He's played 71 of the 72 games in the regular season and here in the plan
21 points on 10 of 18 from the field. He's available every game every year
He plays all the time as Durham is the first team to play in the playoffs
All the time as durable as any player in this league
Kuzma back out to Schroeder shot clock at three puts up the three shot won't go one of the foul
Davis the offensive rebound back up and banks at home
But there's an awful lot of contact
Not just on the shot, but also Davis's rebound and finish Anthony Davis discarded people curry reverse
With the English off the glass a little more magic from Steph Curry. He's got 33
And LeBron James is coming back in
Schroeder drives inside Caruso missed a layup curry the rebound
Curry to Wiggins
Jordan Paul, nope, they wave it off an offensive foul
Sound a screen set by Draymond Green not allowing the chase down contest
James will return
Three fouls on green
Credit to Anthony Davis for not giving up on the play. So his effort to try to get to the shooter forced that call
That's 12 second half turnovers for Golden State. They only had five in the first half
They led by 13 at halftime
Lakers have
Taken the lead here in the fourth. They've led by as many as seven right now all tied with four and a half to play
This is a tough play to guard the curl by Davis Davis knocked away another steal from Draymond Green and
Mulder in the front court
Three steals three blocks for green curry on the drive gets inside foul on jumper. No good
11 rebounds for Davis to go with 21 points
Mulder up and into Schroeder
Drives layup shot is good. Oh, what a tough shot from Schroeder and Draymond Green wanted a push-off
Green's got to be careful with the referees. He already has a technical tonight
Gets the pass from curry
pull for three puts it in
Warriors back up by one and that's where green is great you blitz curry
And
You get it to green and he plays four on three
He's a great great decision maker and it may boil down to just that
Other guys not named curry making shots being ready and aggressive because the Lakers are forcing curry to get rid of the basketball
Dennis Schroeder tries drives on Wiggins flips it up shot. No good rebound rebound Draymond Green
And here come the Warriors up one
with 315 remaining
Curry fakes curry drives floats it up banks at home
Timeout Lakers
Here's the upcoming national TV schedule TNT tomorrow, Indiana and Washington
At Eastern for the right to get into the playoffs then the ESPN on Friday
Memphis winning earlier tonight against San Antonio will play the loser of this game
And it'll be at 9 Eastern for more in these games visit nba.com or the NBA app
This has been a thriller here at the Staples Center
Anthony Davis and the Lakers came back from 13 down took a seven-point lead here on the fourth
But Steph Curry erupting here with a fourth. He's got 35 for the game and it's the Warriors up three and
interestingly Frank Vogel decides to sit Schroeder and
reinsert Wesley Matthews I
Think it's the right move
Absolutely, they got to make an adjustment because the Warriors clearing a side for curry
They have to recognize that defensively the Lakers do and be in position to help James looking to post up Baysmoor
Squares and faces seven on the shot clock
Wiggins looking to help James for on the 24 James jumper short
Rebound Matthews back out to James pass to Caruso corner three side of the backboard and Baysmoor gets the rebound
That talked about it earlier Wiggins forcing LeBron into that shot
That's a shot you're willing to give up if you're the Warriors defensively against a bigger stronger
And Caruso's defense forces the turnovers curry dribbles it out of bounds and
So inside the Davis the runner
No good, but a foul that's absolutely inexcusable on a turnover. They didn't get matched up
So green had to rotate to the wide open Caruso and now Davis gets fouled
So Paul picks up his third and Anthony Davis will shoot free throws
Two for two tonight, it's only 74% during the season
Big
Second half for Davis
Only had five points at halftime
18 in the second half one point game under two and a half remaining
Curry on the drive the floater in the paint short Wiggins tips it but right to Davis
James running the floor
Pass to Caruso back to James and he's fouled
Draymond Green would not let him get a layup and James goes down holding his head
The officials discussing
I think they're going to take a look at it to see if it's a flagrant
And
There's contact to the head of LeBron James
It'd be interesting to see the conclusion that they come up with here
But there's clearly with the right hand of Draymond Green to the head
Goes up the block. This is a huge call again because it will be free throws and possession as green picks up his fourth personal
But clearly to me there was contact on the head according to the rules but not everything to the head is a flagrant foul
You need to make up your mind sir. No, I
Don't think it is one. I think it will be called one and I hate when games are decided on these like
Influenced by like these like they're trying to
Make a difference in the game
And just can we play ball this is a great game absolutely you have covered every base by the way my friend well done
Well James obviously shaken up by the play so he's gonna get two free throws
And he's really get two free throws and will they get possession and he's smart enough to
Make sure they know he's hurt
Oh
I'm gonna name my next son John Gobel. Thank you John bring some sanity back to the NBA
You know and again part of it. It's just such a crucial call for I
Mean he's looking he's going up to block the shot hands down. I think what Steve said there's no wind-up
And he's going up to block the shot hands down. I think what Steve said there's no wind-up
And the impact is because James comes into him and I'm not gonna take I'm not gonna explain myself to the whole LA roster
Play ball. Well James will get the two free throws
I'm not good at Ripley lip reading, but I think he just said something about trouble scene
Though again as Steve Javi said it was a good game
Though again as Steve Javi said it was an awkward fall and that made it look worse than it was and apparently got poked in
the eye to
My only problem with it. It wasn't a contest to the basketball. It was a contest to the face because he can't jump as well
Ties the game with 207 remaining
I've been there before squinting my eyes just in case I miss a free throw so I have an excuse
I've been there
At a rough first half but has made huge plays here in the second half a triple double
misses the second
And a loose ball foul is going to go against lebron james. Jordan pool did a good job pursuing that rebound
And really you look right now both teams are shooting the rest of the way
So you if you're going to be physical defensively you have to be physical and disciplined also
But you don't give up free clothes
Each team with one timeout left and as mark said both teams in the penalty
Baysmoor to pool
wigons green and curry
And an offensive foul call on draymond green on the moving screen west matthews draws that turnover
Steve kerr can't believe that call nor can green who picks up his fifth
And
That's not a legal screen to me that's west matthews selling the foul he's had an important impact on this second half
Caldwell pope back up to james
Wiggins has done an excellent job defensively on him tonight
Shot clock at six james looking to get a running start now pass to caruso caruso on the drive inside davis for the slam
Lakers back up two with a minute and a half to play and caruso has been outstanding outstanding great find
Curry the drive looking to draw contact and he does but they say before the shot doesn't matter. They're in the penalty
So two free throws for curry to tie the game with 123 left
Well, they go back to putting step curry into the pick and roll knowing they don't want to switch it
James came off touched it to caruso who just
Caught it on a stampede to the basket and dropped it off
to davis well anthony davis who had
an awful first half
Has come alive 25 points including
13 here in the fourth quarter as curry hits the free throw and played 41 minutes so far
12 rebounds as well and it's made some excellent defensive plays in the second half
This game has been so much about defense from both teams
Curry ties the game 37 points for step curry
They get it to call well pulp almost lost it shot clock at seven
James two defenders on him to call well pope inside. He's tied up by green throws it back up top. James puts up the three
Oh, it's gone lebron james from downtown
As the shot clock expires
A desperation heave and the lakers are up three
Three
Green back to curry curry sets leans in knocked away get it back from curry shot clock at seven
Baysmore on the drive kicks it out pull for three
James the rebound with 32 seconds remaining
There's about a 10 second different shot clock and game clock. They don't have to foul
I'm lebron james. I'm putting my head down and attacking
Lost the ball gets it back matthews for three
Fight for the rebound tipped twice picked up by pole 10 seconds remaining i'm in a foul
I'm, not letting them shoot a three. They have a timeout left, but we'll call it here
Cur is trying to call it and finally he gets it steve kirk came to half court
The officials couldn't see him or clearly couldn't hear him
And he gets the timeout with 2.1 remaining
We'll see if the officials look to see to perhaps put more time on the clock
They got a great look the last time by jordan pool in the corner off a nice pass by baysmoor
LeBron james with the three-pointer had to throw it up. The shot clock was expiring
So
Big time shot
awful execution
Realizes that the clock dwindling down the good chase down by curry
lebron
Elevates and knocks down the biggest shot of the night. That's a 30-footer and you see curry
Who's had that look on opponent's faces after he knocks down threes the same look as lebron james with a clutch shot
And still talking about his
Difficulty seeing after taking that shot in the face from draymond green
All right, guys, obviously
Golden state needs a three-pointer here to try and force overtime
And for the lakers there's not enough time for them to foul and not allow a three-pointer, correct? It depends on where the ball is caught
And in what position?
I wouldn't be surprised if curry
Is used to try to free somebody else up
Because of team's natural reaction to him
No matter what type of cut he makes and that guy defending the basketball in lebron james in this scenario
I keep my eyes on curry
Baysmoor to inbound
Pool coming free curry trying to get free lost the ball. That's it
The lakers are in the playoffs
The warriors need to play on friday what a thriller here at the staples center
I want to show these two stars put on tonight lebron james with his vision
And
Bothered after that shot from draymond green hits the desperation heave that proved to be the game winner
offsetting the 37 points from steph curry
Lakers will play phoenix on sunday
The warriors will play the grizzlies on friday night to keep their season alive and the respect from the two former mvps
Is
Warriors with an opportunity but
A defensive play ends this one and that's perhaps appropriate with all the terrific defense we saw tonight
This is he didn't even catch it in rhythm
That's just unbelievable just as the shot clock expired and he was blind
So
James with 22 points 11 rebounds 10 assists
And the game winning three-pointer
Is with rachel?
lebron
Congratulations on the win
Nice little celebration there with anthony davis
Yes, sir, you already know
What does this mean to you guys to be officially in the play-in bracket in the playoff bracket and to do it with this kind?
Of win tonight over a team that has really been such a huge rival for you over the second half of your career
Well, I mean going into the postseason. I think it's two of the hottest teams
I think we were winner of five they were winner of uh, seven or eight or whatever the case may be
So both teams playing at a high level and uh, we knew that they're going to come up to our floor and give everything they had
Um, you know, they hit us in the mouth in the first half and we just had to respond and we did that
On the defensive end and uh got some great contributions from guys off the bench. Um, and we all you know chipped in for the
We got to talk about that shot you hit with about a minute left the three you didn't even look in rhythm there
What were you thinking as the ball left your hands?
um, you know just um
I put in a lot of work in my game, you know, um, you know after
You know drape my uh finger to the eye. I was literally seeing three, uh, three rims out there
um, so I just shot at the middle one and uh, and I was able to uh,
The grace of the man above I was able to knock it down
When in doubt go for the middle rim
What did it feel like when you were down there on the floor when you took that hard fall?
Were you worried that you wouldn't be able to continue in the game or have more problems?
You know, i've been there before
Um, you know, i've been poked in the eye before, you know on a rim collision like that. So
Just try to keep my composure, you know, it's going to be pretty sore tonight. I know that for sure
But we have a few days until we do until we know
when we'll go to phoenix, but
It's a big time win for us and I definitely wasn't leaving the floor no matter if I had to
Uh, you know, uh put a pirate, uh patch in my eyes. So
I love this team. I love to compete
One big rivalry down with this win tonight
But you've got another one to go with an old friend in chris paul you mentioned going to phoenix and facing the suns
What do you think that matchup is going to be like?
um, you know, they played, uh, extremely well all year and they deserve to uh,
You know host, uh, you know
home court in the first round
And uh cp, uh, you know played at an mvp
Uh caliber year all year, um book, you know, aden has grown all year and uh, they've given those guys a supporting cast around them
So, you know, uh, we know what we're going to get out of cp. We know how good uh, you know
How great cp is how great book is uh up and coming surgeons from um, you know from aden
You know, but it's the other guys as well that we got to make sure we key in on because they've been playing extremely
Well all year and that's why they've been the second best team in the west. Thank you so much. LeBron
Congratulations. We'll see you in phoenix